OK folks, in this clip I'm going to teach you how to draw a cartoon fly.
I'm going to come right down here in this corner and do it right here.
So, we will start by drawing the rough shape of his head.
And flies have those huge hideous eyes.
So I'm going to like leave room around the top for that.
And also in my mind, flies are not the nicest of creatures.
So we're going to make this guy kind of look a little monstrous.
First we'll add some detail to the eyes here.
We'll come in and we'll draw lines going across, just like this in both directions.
Because flies obviously have several, like I think it's like a hundred eyes or something like that on top of their heads.
So that just creates the illusion of multiple eyes.
And we'll come out and start drawing the rest of his hulking body.
We'll make him sort of like, with his limbs kind of coming off like this.
And their little front ways position.
Draw his lower body, kind of like that.
Hairy, disgusting, warty creature.
No one likes flies.
They are definitely not the most popular insect.
Draw his little legs, like that.
Come down here.
Just kind of make them jagged and ragged.
And then the way we'll draw his wings, seems to me flies sort of have distinct wing shapes, so what we'll do is we'll draw, we'll try to draw his wings as fly shaped as possible.
To really show that this is in fact a fly.
And they're sort of veiny and oddly connected.
So just kind of just get in there and draw some weird sort of connecting, veiny type lines to show that this is an ugly fly.
Reinforce your lines.
And that ought to do it.
Ugly old fly.
So there you go.